courttv.com 2019-08-02

# Privacy Policy - Court TV

Thank you for visiting CourtTV.com, a site presented to you by Katz Broadcasting, LLC, and its affiliates, including Court TV Media, LLC (collectively, “Katz Broadcasting,” “we” or “us”). Your privacy is important to us. This privacy policy explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this general audience Katz Broadcasting site and among Katz Broadcasting’s affiliated and operated websites and applications (each, a “Katz Affiliate Site”), which includes any online or mobile sites, applications or services owned, operated or offered by or on behalf of Katz Broadcasting or its affiliates (each a “Site”, collectively the “Sites”). A list of the entities for which Katz Broadcasting currently operates a Site or Sites (each, a “Katz Affiliate”) is available below.

**– The Information We Collect –**

_Personally Identifiable Information_

At some Katz Affiliate Sites, you may be able to enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters or text message alerts, participate in one of our online forums or communities, or order products. In the course of these various offerings, we often seek to collect from you various forms of personally identifiable information. Examples of the types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number and credit card information.

At some Katz Affiliate Sites, you may also be able to submit personally identifiable information about other people. For example, you might submit a person’s name and e-mail address to send an electronic greeting card and, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you might submit the recipient’s name and address. Examples of the types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient’s name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number.

At certain parts of some Katz Affiliate Sites, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to order products or otherwise participate in the site’s activities and offerings.

We do not knowingly collect or store any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child under the age of 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information without the consent of the parent or guardian, the parent or guardian may contact us at privacy@ScrippsTV.com and we will delete the child’s personally identifiable information within a reasonable time.

_Non-Personally Identifiable Information_

When you visit our Sites, we, our third-party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, and partners may collect various types of information that are anonymous or otherwise not intended to personally identify you (“Non-Personally Identifiable Information”). Non-Personally Identifiable Information may include information such as: network or Internet protocol address and type of browser you are using (e.g., Chrome, Safari, Firefox, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Microsoft Windows or Mac OS), the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., Comcast, Verizon or AT&T), mobile network, device identifiers, advertising identifiers, the web pages of the Katz Affiliate Sites you have visited, sites visited before and after you visit a Katz Affiliate Site, the type of handheld or mobile device used to view the Site (e.g., iPhone, Blackberry), general location information (e.g., city, county, and/or state), and content and advertisements you have accessed, seen, forwarded and/or clicked on.

_Geo-location Information_

If you are accessing a Katz Affiliate Site from a mobile device or through a mobile application, you may be asked to share your geo-location information with us so we can customize your experience on our Sites. If you agree to such collection, you will be able to turn off such data collection at any time by accessing the privacy settings of your mobile device and/or through the settings in the applicable mobile application.

_Information from Social Networks and Platforms_

You also can engage with our content, such as video, games, applications, and other offerings, on or through third-party platforms and social networking sites, such as Facebook, or other third-party social media plug-ins and applications. When you engage with our content on or through third party social networking sites, plug-ins or applications, you may allow us to have access to certain personally identifiable information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information from your social media profile (e.g., name, e-mail address, photo, gender, birthday, location, user files like photos and videos, your list of friends, people you follow and/or who follow you, the posts or the ‘likes’ you make, etc.) to deliver the content or as part of the operation of the Site. From your interaction with our content, we may also obtain Non-Personally Identifiable Information (e.g., content viewed, game scores, and information about advertisements within the content you have been shown or may have clicked on through third-party platforms).

Through some social networking sites’ privacy settings, you can control what information you share. For a description on how social networking sites handle your information, please refer to their privacy policies and terms of use.

**How We Use the Information**

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you, to enforce the legal terms that govern your use of our Sites, and/or for the purposes for which you provided the information.

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter or notification, or to contact you about your account with us.

We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your gifts or cards or emails you may wish to send them from our Sites, and for such other purposes as may be stated at the point where the information is collected.

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, services or customized experiences.

If you choose to submit content for publication (for example, a posting to a blog or a discussion board, or a video), we may publish your screen name, email address, or other information you have provided to us. We may on occasion combine information we collect through our Sites with information that we collect from other sources. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, if you register and create a profile with our Sites, the screen name you select as well as other content you submit to your profile (e.g., photos, comments, video, reviews) will be displayed publicly on the Sites and may be reused and redistributed by us in our sole discretion, as set forth in our Terms of Use.

We, the Katz Affiliates, our third-party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, or our partners use the Non-Personally Identifiable Information that is collected to improve the design and content of our Sites, to deliver more relevant marketing messages and advertisements, to enable us to personalize your Internet experience, and to perform analytics. We also may use this information to analyze usage of our Sites or content, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.

When you provide information from your social media account, it can help enable us to do things like (1) give you exclusive content, (2) personalize your online experience with us within and outside our Sites, (3) contact you through the social networking sites or directly by sending you the latest news, special offerings, and rewards, and (4) enable you to share your experience and content via social networking sites. By doing so, you consent to the use of this information in accordance with our privacy statement. When you provide personally identifiable information to us through an application, on our Sites, or on social networking sites, it may be publicly viewed by other members of these sites and we cannot prevent further use of the information by third parties.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1).

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

We may disclose information we have collected from you or the device used to access the Sites in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or where we believe in our sole discretion it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Sites and applicable laws or as otherwise required or permitted by law or consistent with legal requirements.

In addition, we may transfer information if we, or one of our business units, are acquired by, sold to, merged with or otherwise transferred to another entity.

Our agents and contractors who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this personally identifiable information in a manner that is consistent with this privacy statement and are not authorized to use the personally identifiable information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for us.

We may disclose personally identifiable information and/or Non-Personally Identifiable Information to third parties whose practices are not covered by this privacy statement. For example, we may share such personally identifiable information we collect with Katz Affiliates to provide, improve and communicate with you about their own products and services. A representative list of our affiliates is available in the Katz Affiliates section below.

We may also share such information with unaffiliated business partners and third parties (e.g., other marketers, magazine publishers, retailers, participatory databases, and non-profit organizations) that want to market products or services to you. If a Katz Affiliate Site shares personally identifiable information with such unaffiliated third parties, it will provide you with an opportunity to opt out or block such uses either at the point of submission of your personally identifiable information or prior to any such disclosure.

If you have signed up to receive our e-mails and prefer not to receive marketing information from this Site, follow the “unsubscribe” instructions provided on any marketing e-mail you receive from this Site. If you have signed up to receive text messages from us and no longer wish to receive such messages, you may follow the instructions to stop the delivery of such messages, which may include by replying “STOP” to the received text message.

Katz Affiliate Sites covered by this privacy statement may offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, promotions, games, applications, or social network integrations) that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the Site’s activity. We have no control over these third parties’ use of this information. The Site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such personally identifiable information.

To provide visitors with additional or more relevant product and service opportunities, to improve and personalize the Sites and to perform analytics, and for the additional uses discussed in this privacy statement, we may share Non-Personally Identifiable Information with the Katz Affiliates, third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, or our partners.

**Cookies, Web Beacons, Analytics and Advertising**

To enhance your online experience, we use “cookies” or similar technologies. Cookies are text files placed in your computer’s browser to store your preferences.

We use cookies to understand Site and Internet usage and to improve or customize the content, offerings or advertisements on our Sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our Sites (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to a Site), to save your password in password-protected areas, and to enable you to use shopping carts on our Sites. We also may use cookies to help us offer you products, programs, or services that may be of interest to you and to deliver relevant advertising.

We, our third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, or our partners also may use cookies to manage and measure the performance of advertisements displayed on or delivered by or through the Katz Affiliate Sites. This also helps us, our service providers and partners provide more relevant advertising.

The Adobe Flash Player is web tool that allows rapid development of highly dynamic content. Katz Affiliate Sites employ locally stored objects (sometimes referred to as “Flash cookies”) in certain situations where we use Flash to provide special content such as video streaming, video on demand, video clips or animation. Flash (and similar applications) use this technology to remember settings, preferences and usage similar to browser cookies, but Flash cookies are not managed through your web browser. You can access your Flash management tools from Adobe’s website directly.

We, our third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies or our partners may also use “web beacons,” clear .gifs or similar technologies, which are small pieces of code placed on a Site or in an email, to monitor the behavior and collect data about the visitors viewing a Site or email. For example, web beacons may be used to count the users who visit a web page or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a visitor viewing that Site. Web beacons may also be used to provide information on the effectiveness of our email campaigns (e.g., open rates, clicks, forwards, etc.).

**How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals**

At this time the Katz Affiliate Sites do not recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking mechanisms, which may include “do not track” instructions. However, you can change your privacy preferences regarding the use of cookies and similar technologies through your browser. You may set your browser to accept all cookies, block certain cookies, require your consent before a cookie is placed in your browser, or block all cookies. Blocking all cookies will affect your online experience and may prevent you from enjoying the full features offered at Katz Affiliate Sites. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information.

**Analytics**

We also use the services of reputable third parties to provide us with data collection, reporting, ad response measurement, and website and mobile application analytics, as well as to assist with delivery of relevant marketing messages and advertisements. These third parties may view, edit or set their own cookies. We, our third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies and/or partners may also place web beacons or similar technologies for these third parties. The use of these technologies by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by this privacy statement.

**Advertising**

The Katz Affiliate Sites may contain advertising. Ads on the Katz Affiliate Sites may be based on the content of pages you are viewing, but we may also provide ads that are tailored to your interests. To help us deliver ads that are of interest to you, we, the Katz Affiliates, our third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, or our partners may collect information about your online activities across the Katz Affiliate Sites and other sites, and supplement this information with information from third parties.

**Mobile Device Advertising and Tracking**

We, our third-party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, or our partners may also collect identifiers designed to enable advertising on your mobile device. Depending on your device, you may be able to reset your mobile device’s advertising identifier by accessing the privacy settings on your mobile device. In addition, when using a mobile application you may receive tailored in-application advertisements. Each operating system, iOS for Apple phones, Android for Android devices and Windows for Microsoft devices, provides its own instructions on how to prevent the delivery of tailored in-application advertisements. You may review the support materials and/or the privacy settings for the respective operating systems in order to opt-out of tailored in-application advertisements. For any other devices and/or operating systems, please visit the privacy settings for the applicable device or contact the applicable platform operator.

**Linked Sites**

Some Katz Affiliate Sites may contain links to or integrations with other sites, such as Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, or sites operated by other third parties. The information practices of these sites on may be different from ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

**Our Commitment to Security**

We have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect online. These safeguards vary based on the sensitivity of the information that we collect and store.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this privacy statement.

**How You Can Access or Correct Information**

Access to personally identifiable information that is collected from our Sites and that we maintain may be available to you. For example, if you created a password-protected account within our Site, you can access that account to review the information you provided.

You may also send an e-mail or letter requesting access to or correction of your personally identifiable information to the e-mail or street address designated below under How to Contact Us. For verification purposes please include your first name, last name, e-mail address and the password you use for such service.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about the online privacy statement for this site or its implementation you may contact us at:

Katz Broadcasting, LLC  
ATTN: Privacy Coordinator  
2870 Peachtree Road #334  
Atlanta, Georgia 30305  
Email: privacy@ScrippsTV.com  
Phone: 470-355-8718

**California Residents – Your California Privacy Rights**

If you are a California resident, you may request information about our practices related to disclosing your personally identifiable information to certain third parties and/or opt-out of our sharing of your personally identifiable information with unaffiliated third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. Please send your request (along with your full name, e-mail address, postal address, and the subject line labeled “California Privacy Rights”) by e-mail to privacy@ScrippsTV.com.

**Katz Broadcasting Affiliates**

Below is a list of entities for which Katz Broadcasting operates one or more Sites and that currently may have access to the information collected from users on the Katz Affiliate Sites as explained in this privacy statement:

Bounce Media, LLC

Brown Sugar, LLC 

Court TV Media, LLC   
Escape Media, LLC  
Grit Media, LLC  
LAFF Media, LLC

Trumpet 25, LLC 

We may update this list from time to time, so please check back periodically to keep up-to-date.

**Updates & Effective Date**

From time to time, we may update this privacy statement. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this statement so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use the information, and with whom we share it.

The Privacy Statement posted on this Site was updated on March 6, 2019.
